

## **Objective**

A creative, talented and ambitious web professional with 5+ years' experience in designing and coding for the web who seeks to apply those skills and improve every day in order to create quality products and grow both self as a professional and clients.

# **Experience**

## Senior Front-End Developer @ Pool.Garden

5/2021 - Present

### **Chia Cryptocurrency Farming Pool**

Designed the UI for this Chia crypto currency farming pool. Develop the front end using Next.js and work in coordination with devops engineer to maintain a crypto pool service.

## Marketing Web Developer @ Firewalls.com

8/2019 - Present

#### Firewalls Reseller & Service Provider

Built and maintained a Magento 2 ecommerce website. Oversee 3 developers and contribute to building a Laravel 8 application, using Vue3 for the front end and Docker for dev environment.

# Front-End Developer @ BitLoft

8/2016 - 8/2019

#### **Software Development Company**

Worked specifically with Laravel 5, assisted in building a customer management tool. Designed and coded wordpress websites and assisted with UX Design and Interaction Design.

# Web Designer @ 4Media

2/2015 - 5/2016

#### Web & Media Agency

Built various mobile responsive websites using tools like bootstrap and LESS for local and international clients.

# **Graphic Designer @ JC Marketing**

7/2014 - 8/2016 (Freelance, Part Time)

#### **Social Media Company**

Worked remotely to provide social media graphics and web design consulting.

### Education

# BA, Visual Effects & Motion Graphics

2009-2012

The Art Institute Of Fort Lauderdale.

### **About Me**

✔ N/A On Web Resume

✓ N

robertkregloh.com

## **Technologies**

NextJS, Vue3, HTML, CSS, SCSS, LESS, JavaScript, jQuery, Flexbox, CSS Grid, Laravel 8, Docker.

## Languages

English, Spanish

### **Skills**

Responsive Web Design, User Experience, Front End Development, Interaction Design, Frameworks, Version Control, Testing and Debugging, Browser Developer Tools. Command Line, Video Editing, Prototyping, Planning, Story Mapping

### **Tools**

Adobe Suite, Sublime Text, GIT, Jira, VS Code, Wordpress CMS, Laravel, Lumen, Bootstrap, Google Cloud Platform, Trello

### Methods

Agile/Scrum, Kanban